I'm going to say council for Tuesday 1, 2020, but I'm to proclamation declaring April 2025 as autism awareness and take acceptance month.
We must hear accepted.
Motion to approve.
Second.
Gentleman.
Mark.
Five.
Three.
Public input.
I'm scared of personal promises.
We have one.
Lisa.
Mark.
We're here.
Yeah.
I think we can choose.
So that was handled before the meeting.
Yes, sir.
Four.
Plains list.
First to approve.
Say.
Fifth.
Don't call.
Hi.
Jones.
I.
Farms.
Five.
Plains list.
Fifth.
Don't call.
Farms.
My.
Jones.
I.
Six.
Child.
First.
etical.
Second.
Next.
Zeiss.
Second.
Third.
and $625 from the carryover in the REC fund to purchase a new tarp for the new gym floor.
The motion to approve.
Thank you.
All right.
Jones.
A step.
Go.
Parker.
Hey, contract with.
I'm going to ask a lot about when we're going to do it, so I'd like to get it on the calendar.
I did ask this time that we out of Friday, so it's Friday, Saturday, Sunday, May 2nd, 3rd and 4th this year.
And if you guys had approved, we'll get the word out that that's the weekend.
I did contact the Miami News record they traditionally have hosted it, but if they haven't, the last couple years, but they are aware if they want to do anything special for it.
I'll try to put it on all of our city stuff and get the word out and let me straighten out this morning that we were doing that, so they could maybe add to whatever they want to do.
So anyway, I just need your approval to get the word out.
Nice to meet you.
James, I'm sorry.
Sorry, sorry.
He said double.
Hi.
Parker, are you a weekman?
James, discussion about the actual action we are in for General Conflicts, the city attorney representing the city, council, and the GFA.
So I was asked to review contracts for the access of agreement with the at the football field and I got a contract on my desk that was between the city council and MCFA.
And I was asked to review it on behalf of MCFA.
I'm not well, I can't do that.
If there were a bridge of contract action or some other litigation, I can't represent both.
And that made me think, I wonder if there's a conflict of interest for me representing all of the different boards really along with the city council.
Because the main method there is some adverse action that would not be kosher.
I could not represent both in a safe bridge of contract action.
So I called the Oklahoma Bar Association Ethics Council, and we talked about it.
One of these small.
There is a way that I can represent both, but that is what implied written consent.
And I've drafted an implied written consent that I think MCFA.
will be signing tomorrow but I'm not sure I can't speak the board but that also requires
the City Council to weigh the potential communications to me with regards to these boards
with not the confidential management to the big deal.
Does that because they're a decision-making board?
Yes.
Yeah, the boards that are advisory, it's not an issue but it could potentially be with MSUA
in the future.
This is just, I've only raised this discussion to not with regards to MCFA because that's the one
that's immediately on the in the spot with respect to this particular contract.
I've contacted Ken Williams and he will read the contract on behalf of MCFA.
No, I will read on behalf of MCFA, he'll read on behalf of the City just to get through
these contracts but this council needs to be aware and discussed this.
I would actually recommend that we've really table this before action and I can send or
milliseconds and copies of the prepared conflict white vote to you review it because it's a
big deal.
Now, contact will then then said he never really considered it a conflict because there is such a low
chance that the two entities would end up in any sort of adverse litigation but the ethics council
of our association partially disagree.
The waiver is in their packet and waiver is in the packet.
Oh, that's for us.
You said that you were going to do so you have to go and I would note that if you sign that, if you agree
to the waiver, that covers most things that are encompassed in my job but should there be litigation
in the future, I would be materially barred.
I would have a material issue with representing you because I would have already received
information from the other side that could be used against you so you would have to have
So that sort of representation, there will be a material limitation that's a lot.
Or do you have the shoulders happening with?
I think MSUIA is the one that I'm most concerned about.
About any voting board there could be...
In the RA, any voting board there could be a problem with it.
The likelihood of it, I think, is the greatest with MSUIA.
I agree with Ben that there's not a likely problem or...
I'm not going to end up in court, the city and the MCF.
I just don't see that happening.
It's not likely.
But when you get utilities and the kind of money involved with the MSUIA, there could be a problem.
Now that's less than about the fact that this board is in USA and MSUIA, especially in court.
So that's greatly less than about that.
But if there were going to be problems with that.
I think the recommendation of my council, we should table it, right?
I think it should be table to allow you to look into it yourself.
And it even says that you're encouraged in there to seek on the council.
And Ken Williams is already aware of the situation, so that would be the likelihood on this.
Well, it comes about the conflict here.
In light of this possibility, Council would recommend full party seek in a cash legal advice group.
Yeah.
I have to put that in there.
Well, that's good.
I mean, that's what we have.
And the event that...
I mean, typically where this comes up has come up in mind.
And, you know, it's more appropriate.
I know that there's no money even.
I just want to get it done.
But this is...
Yeah, we're just...
We're just going to take it on.
We can take it up on it.
I just want to put you aware of that.
I think it's in a sign of that.
11.
Discussion about the election.
I'm going to see 20-0-8-C.
Let me through the instruction.
And see 23-0-8-C.
Let's go and model those services.
That's the sign of the album.
Motion to approve.
Second.
Is that...
Hi.
Farms.
Jones.
Hi.
Purple.
Well, about the new business.
If any of this brings this position, this gives it 13 staff reports.
working, they're a castle, we have the Spring Market Pass Board, there's 25 businesses I believe
downtown that are participating, so you go down there, there's lots of gifts to give me
way and different things and that's kind of a cool deal. We talked about that briefly today.
And then we're looking at May 1st for the public meeting for our rates, we talked about
the public meeting and I was willing to see what the board thought about. We should bring
community fiber during that meeting too and to see from just to the community, this is what we're looking at.
I think there would be a big support for it, so it is all I have here.
If you're staying in May 1st, we'll not be continuing from Calth Chambers, we're going to be in the
staff for the public executive session. If you place any other regular meeting of the mine and
that's for all the public facilities for the board.